

39 Coft An Righ, KY11 1PF, Inverkeithing

#### CONTACT



(+44) 7917102483 (+420) 724 375 576



jjancickova@gmail.com

### VOLUNTEERING

ACE IT, Project Work Wise - couch

The City of Edinburgh Council, Project Get Online couch, private sessions

# JULIE JANCICKOVA

#### **ABOUT**

I am a motivated and hardworking software developer and designer student (at Edinburgh College). Work experience in retail and other customer-facing roles has provided a sense of good customer service and good manner. I am an organized person with good communication skills and a positive attitude. I have experience working as a part of a team and individually, and I can handle multiple tasks daily.

Furthermore, I am reliable and adaptable to changing and busy environments. I specialize in creating a friendly and receptive atmosphere in the workplace.

#### **EDUCATION**

EDINBURGH COLLEGE (CAMPUS GRANTON) - UK, SCOTLAND

| SCQF level 8 | 2022- PRESENT

Course: HND Digital Design and Development

EDINBURGH COLLEGE (CAMPUS GRANTON) - UK, SCOTLAND

| SCQF level 6 | 2021- 2022

Course: NPA Software Development and Digital Design

HIGH SCHOOL OF TRANSPORT PRAGUE MOTOL - CZECH REPUBLIC

A-level equivalent (accomplishment of Maturita exam) | 2011 - 2015 Course: Economy and Public Transport

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

SYFT AGENCY - BARISTA, BARISTA, WAITING STAFF, CUSTOMER SERVICE Flexible | Mar 2022 - PRESENT

- Managing tasks depending on the chosen role
- Helping and working in different environments regarding the company policies, roles require being able to adapt quickly and adjust to new team members/management

KIMPTON HOTEL - BARTENDER (DURING FULL-TIME COLLEGE COURSE) Kimpton Hotel - Edinburgh | Jun 2021 - Apr 2022

- Mixing, garnishing, and serving alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks
- taking orders and making guests feel taken care of during their visit
- greeting customers, learning about their preferences, answering questions, making recommendations

WAREHOUSE OPERATIVE - CUSTOMER RETURNS/PROBLEM SOLVE Amazon UK Services Ltd. - EDI14 | Nov 2020 - May 2021

- Processed and inspected returned items in an internal software
- Made decisions about items based on customer's comment or condition of an item

### **CORE QUALIFICATION**

Bitmap Graphic Design Authorising a Website Animation Fundamentals Vector Graphic Programming (SQL 6) Math for Software Developers

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Czech - Mother tongue English - Advanced

### **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Clean driving licence (active driver) Interested in Photography, editing, photo-manipulation and graphic design

Advance user of Microsoft Suite (especially Word, Excel , Power Point, Access)

Advance User Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Animate, Premier Pro, XD and InDesign) High level of experience in Customer Service

## **PERSONAL QUALITIES**

Creative
Quick learner
Team player
Initiative
Communicative
Reliable

#### RETAIL SALES ASSISTANT

The Nutckracker Christmas Shop Edinburgh | Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

- Processed sales, exchanges, and refunds
- Helped customers made purchasing decisions by offering suggestions
- Worked well under pressure; especially during the Christmas period when the store was at its busiest
- Completing transactions at the checkout

#### BARTENDER/WAITRESS

The Restaurant Mudlark - London Bridge | Jan 2019 - Sep 2019

- Served each guest with a pleasant and positive attitude
- Delivered an exceptional level of service to each customer by listening to concerns and answering questions
- Maitland full knowledge of menu items
- Processed cash, credit cards, and vouchers payments
- Oversaw bar inventory, restocked supplies, and placed orders
- Prepared and served drinks and cocktails
- Trained and supervised new staff

#### MACHINE OPERATOR

HEEMSKERK Fresh & Easy - Rijnsburg, Netherlands | Nov 2017 - Dec 2018

- Operated machines of various food processing in a busy factory setting (ensuring all machines are working to their optimal settings, to reduce downtime)
- Adhered to health and safety regulations whilst ensuring that production is optimal
- Trained and helped new staff to achieved company goals

# ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, CUSTOMER SERVICE AND TECHNICAL SUPPORT Connect Plus s.r.o. - Prague, Czech Republic | Mar 2016 - Oct 2017

- Provided administrative support (scheduled meetings, appointments, and transport)
- Managed daily calendar (meetings, installations)
- Received and answered emails and correspondence from clients and handled internal communication
- Answered and directed calls
- Managed weekly calendar (meetings, installations)
- Drove client feedback to deliver information to management for corrective action
- Resolved customer problems and complaint (suggested optional loyalty offers)

# RECEPTIONIST, ADMINISTRATIVE SUPPORT

PRO.MED.CS Praha AS - Prague, Czech Republic | May 2015 - Feb 2016

- Greeted incoming visitors and clients professionally and provided friendly, knowledgeable assistance
- Answered telephone calls (multi-line telephone system)
- Answered questions, resolved or escalated issues to the management to satisfy customers
- Aggregated and prepared documentation and reports for office meetings, distribution and filing